export const Flashcards = [
{
    Question: "Ready?",
    Answer: "Hit next to begin",
    img:"card"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Zeus?",
    Answer: "Jupiter",
    img:"Zeus"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Hera?",
    Answer: "Juno",
    img:"Hera"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Athena?",
    Answer: "Minerva",
    img:"Athena"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Poseidon?",
    Answer: "Neptune",
    img:"Poseidon"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Apollo?",
    Answer: "Apollo",
    img:"Apollo"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Ares?",
    Answer: "Mars",
    img:"Ares"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Demeter?",
    Answer: "Ceres",
    img:"Demeter"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Artemis?",
    Answer: "Diana",
    img:"Artemis"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Hephaestus?",
    Answer: "Vulcan",
    img:"Hephaestus"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Aphrodite?",
    Answer: "Venus",
    img:"Aphrodite"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Hermes?",
    Answer: "Mercury",
    img:"Hermes"
},
{
    Question: "What is the Roman name of Dionysus?",
    Answer: "Bacchus",
    img:"Dionysus"
},

];